bodystrength.com 2014-02-14

# Body Strength | Privacy Policy

Body Strength understands the protection of your privacy is part of your decision making process when visiting websites. This privacy policy will tell you what information we collect and what you do for Body Strength. It explains your choices in the protection your privacy and information and how we use this information. We urge you to read this policy completely, so you have no questions on the terms and procedures on Body Strength.

This privacy policy covers the information that Body Strength gathers from you when you are on our site. This policy covers the information we share with business partners, but will not be the policy third parties abide by.

Our goal in collecting personal information is to: personalize and improve the services provided on Body Strength, respond to your feedback and customize your experience with Body Strength.

We collect the following information when you visit:

  1. Information You Provide: This includes information that you provide us when you submit goals, questions, answers. To do so, you must register with Body Strength. Registering includes your name and email address. Creating a user profile allows us to better find information that fits your needs and interests. 
  2. Automatically Collected: We take note of your IP address, browser type, timestamp information, pages viewed and searches made. This information is collected, so we can better understand you as a user. 

We will never lease, rent, sell or otherwise trade your information to outside parties.

We reserve the right to transfer non-personally identifiable information to companies that share our privacy policy. These companies include: our current or future affiliates, parent company, joint ventures, subsidiaries or companies under common control.

We are affiliated with businesses that we do not control. These third parties do not abide by our privacy policy because they follow their own. These companies may decide to display advertisements on our site. If you decide to click on a third party advertisement, we are no longer responsible for the safety and protection of your information.

We believe the protection of children is important. Therefore, we follow the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. Under COPPA, we will never collect any personal information from users under the age of 13.

Protecting yourself on the internet is a two-way street. It is responsibility of both the user and the site administrators. Under the California Online Privacy Protection Act, also known as the “Shine the Light Act,” we will never transfer your information to outside parties without your authentication.

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy as we see fit. If we do so, these revisions will be posted on this page. You will always see the most recent version of this policy.

Your interaction with Body Strength is solely up to you. If you decide you no longer have interest in Body Strength, you may unsubscribe from all communication with us. Please do so at the following link: Unsubscribe

Questions may come up and we will do our best to facilitate them. Visit our Contact Us page to contact us about any questions or concerns you have.
